<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>PersonalGrowth on MH Creator</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/personalgrowth/</link>
        <description>Recent content in PersonalGrowth on MH Creator</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 15:17:19 +0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/personalgrowth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Why Women Shouldn’t Lower Their Standards in Relationships</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/my-fifteen-post/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 15:17:19 +0500</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/my-fifteen-post/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/0015.png" alt="Featured image of post Why Women Shouldn’t Lower Their Standards in Relationships" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, I want to argue a point of view that I have been hearing a lot for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Which is:&lt;/strong&gt; Women need to lower their standards, especially when it comes to relationships!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I want to suggest something to all the guys who say this and relationship coaches — especially: why don’t you say this instead? &amp;ldquo;Read Below.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;main-points&#34;&gt;Main Points
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why don&amp;rsquo;t you say to the guys who cannot find an understandable woman:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be polite. No need for money or status — representing yourself with politeness is one way to get through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Humor is an amazing personality trait to have! But know how to use it properly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Education degree is good, but if you have good understanding of your surroundings and how to utilize problem solving with critical thinking in a calm way, then I am sorry not sorry — put your degree in a cup of water and drink it. Maybe it will be useful. Hypothetically, a way to at least drink the knowledge since your brilliant mind could not have the benefits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do work on upgrading your knowledge, and these days you have plenty of ways to do it. Read a book, watch documentaries, involve yourself in workshops, or learn a craft. Make yourself useful to her. I know people who have nothing to brag about except their good behavior and usefulness, and women agree on what they have. And I can see that she is way smarter than him, and I believe he knows it — yet he is not downsizing her. Instead, he is also using her knowledge for his life tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lastly, guys, as you are asking for things, make sure you meet what she asks for! Because this is what made the standard higher.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Girls, have your standard met. If he agrees and asks for time to meet your standard, understand him — give him time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What I mean here by standards is not money, status, or fame. No, I mean behavior-wise, maturity, emotional intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;1- Tip: Ask her, who is your favorite actor? If she says anything about the character he played, listen to her — she is telling you about the way of treating her, okay!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If she said otherwise, then it is up to you if you want to stay or leave. She is materialistic if you are thinking to have an understanding one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2- Tip: Watch this &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0406046/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;movie&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt13911628/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;series&lt;/a&gt;. Look please at what the male character did to show his usefulness and understanding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;-mh&#34;&gt;– MH
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;links&#34;&gt;Links
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📬 &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;mahaakab@gmail.com&#34; &gt; Email Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;☕ &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/c/MHCreator&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt; Coffee Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>What’s the Point of Living? – A Follow-up with Philosophy</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/my-eleven-post/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 20:25:58 +0500</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/my-eleven-post/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/0011.png" alt="Featured image of post What’s the Point of Living? – A Follow-up with Philosophy" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Switching to a Saturday Blog!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to change my weekly blog from Friday to Saturday, simply because that&amp;rsquo;s what has been happening naturally for a while now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today’s blog is one of the possible answers to the question I asked last week: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://mhcreator.github.io/my-ten-post/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;What Is the Point of Living?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;healing-through-philosophy---التداوي-بالفلسفة&#34;&gt;Healing Through Philosophy - التداوي بالفلسفة
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This book was a recommendation from an influencer I follow. Interestingly, when I studied Philosophy in university, I didn’t enjoy it much and barely remember what it was about. So, before even starting this book, I was skeptical.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was actually searching for another book, but since I couldn’t find it in PDF format, I decided to give Healing Through Philosophy (التداوي بالفلسفة) a try. I had time to read while waiting for my brother at the dentist. T_T&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;📖 Note: The book is in Arabic (my native language). I’m not sure if it’s available in English or other languages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The author, Saeed Nashid, did an amazing job using his own insights combined with ideas from notable philosophers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Chapter That Got Me: &amp;ldquo;Maybe We Don&amp;rsquo;t Need Hope&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this chapter, Nashid references a story from The Book of Samuel II (Old Testament) about Prophet David and how he reacted when his son (before Solomon) was ill and later died. His followers were surprised by his shift in emotions—from distress to calmness. He explained that once his son passed away, he no longer had to witness his suffering. Instead, he found comfort in knowing that he would reunite with him in the afterlife.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The philosophical idea here is how hope can be a double-edged sword—it can motivate us, but it can also cause emotional suffering when things don’t turn out as we expect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The book also references Jean-Jacques Rousseau, Friedrich Nietzsche, and Baruch Spinoza. Nietzsche, for example, pointed out that the ancient Greeks believed hope was the greatest evil—because it keeps people waiting instead of acting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My Thoughts on Hope&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This chapter hit me because nowadays, &amp;ldquo;hope&amp;rdquo; is marketed everywhere—in self-help books, social media, and even corporate culture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But in reality, hope alone is not enough. Life isn’t a movie where everything magically works out. Most of our days are filled with routine, boredom, and occasional happiness—and too much hope can lead to disappointment when things don’t happen as expected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This book gave me one possible answer to last week’s question. It presents a lifestyle perspective, where people try to define meaning in every aspect of life—whether it’s happiness, career, love, or marriage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It also helped me understand how ideas evolve over time—how people in the past thought vs. how modern society thinks today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But here’s my struggle:
There are so many concepts in philosophy, and after understanding them, I have to decide how to apply them in my own life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The book is short—so if you find it in your language, I highly recommend reading it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until next week, just take it easy. 😊&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;links&#34;&gt;Links
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📬 &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;mahaakab@gmail.com&#34; &gt; Email Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;☕ &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/c/MHCreator&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt; Coffee Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>My Artistic Path! Blender, Social Media, and Self-Doubt</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/my-seven-post/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 20:45:31 +0500</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/my-seven-post/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/0007.png" alt="Featured image of post My Artistic Path! Blender, Social Media, and Self-Doubt" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;People pleasing planet got a million people saying how to plan it&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;Imagine Dragons&amp;rdquo;. I am vibing with their song today. 🎧♫♪♫&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, today&amp;rsquo;s weather was nice; windy + the sun shone brightly with a pinch of clouds and flowers starting to bloom again. &amp;ldquo;Grateful Face&amp;rdquo;☀️🌾🤗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Actully, I am struggling with what to write for this blog! I was thinking of writing about my favorite anime! But no it&amp;rsquo;s going to be a lot and I feel tired now, maybe because of I just had my dinner.🥱😴&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, this blog post will be about pursuing my creative passion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-it-did-grow-on-me&#34;&gt;How It did Grow on me!
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Learning 3D art with Blender beginning was the Donut tutorial from &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@blenderguru&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Blender Guru&lt;/a&gt;. I remember working on it for the first time and was around 2020 since I was unemployed hehe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Honestly, I wanted this time to last forever.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, you know we humans are a very difficult species! Or maybe it is just me.
I felt unhonest. Like it is a lie I&amp;rsquo;m telling to myself, that being an digital artist is not my interest. Literally, this is what I told myself that I was just going to use my free time in this, and I&amp;rsquo;ll apply for real jobs like the one that was in my mind Content Writing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;guess-what-&#34;&gt;Guess What! 😔
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After I believe 6 months of creating 3D models with Blender, I have stopped!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Writing about this now makes me realize the heartache. Because.. yeah when I started the job I was into it, to know all the ins and outs then shifted to another position as a Social Media Executive. This position too got me excited to work with dynamic creative writing with social media, I was fascinatie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yet, doing all by being busy with work and my studies, I still felt the urge that I was doing something wrong, it&amp;rsquo;s not what I wanted to do. And from all the things I was interested in, my interest in 3D did not die. I was following the Blender Guru newsletter and following **&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.blender.org/features/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Blender&lt;/a&gt;**news always checking out their yearly event for updates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To sum up this Blog, I am going to say two things to overcoming self-doubt in creativity. 😎👌🔥&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, don&amp;rsquo;t you ever leave yourself without an interest, and if you find it &lt;strong&gt;Do Not&lt;/strong&gt; let yourself foul you. That it&amp;rsquo;s not what you are supposed to do, I am still trying to stop myself! Even after I made up my mind that this is what I want to be doing till I leave this earth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dont miss this sign; if you are feeling happy while doing it.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keep doing it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Secondly, I have an account on Instagram, which I intend to share my beginner&amp;rsquo;s journey in digital art in 2D and intermediate in 3D. As I left my last job position as assistant manager in the Social Media Team, I thought doing social media for yourself was really easy. No, it&amp;rsquo;s not, even with experience in social media, becasue I can be lazy. &amp;ldquo;I try my best&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And this time I leave you with this:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“ If you hear a voice within you say you cannot paint, then by all means paint and that voice will be silenced.” ― Van Gogh&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;links&#34;&gt;Links
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🌐 &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.behance.net/makcreator&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Behance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📬 &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;mahaakab@gmail.com&#34; &gt; Email Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;☕ &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/c/MHCreator&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt; Coffee Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How Anime Inspired My Passion for the Japanese Language | Part 3</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/my-sixth-post/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 17:00:13 +0500</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/my-sixth-post/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/0006.png" alt="Featured image of post How Anime Inspired My Passion for the Japanese Language | Part 3" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To be honest I don&amp;rsquo;t know how to start this blog post! But in this blog post, I want to share about the scholarships that I am applying for to achieve my Dream of Studying in Japan for my higher education.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-story-with-japanese-scholarships&#34;&gt;My Story with Japanese Scholarships!
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I started applying last year to any opportunity I could find&amp;hellip; and I have started with the most popular MEXT scholarship journey began with embassy track! I passed the exam section, and the interview section, but then not accepted with the nomination section of MEXT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did not feel tearful when it happened because it&amp;rsquo;s scholarships and the count of people who were is many. And there was the university track! Yet, I remember telling myself, that I must have said something in the interview or maybe because my Japanese Language was beginner since I could not attend the exam accurately. Or it could be that they do not accept my field of study&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It does not make any difference at the end of the day I had to just take it easy and do what I had to do. I&amp;rsquo;ll apply for this year also when it opens..&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;University track&lt;/strong&gt; was no good also!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because the field they were offering the scholarship was not my study field. I did my search and looked for universities that can offer the field and the scholarship and I did the second part of e-mailing the professor&amp;hellip; got one response who told me he is retiring and can&amp;rsquo;t have me; the other no reply till now!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here I am not complaining I am stating the facts only.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next&lt;/strong&gt;
Yesterday that date 5/2/2025 morning I had another inconsolable news!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After, my ADB-JSP scholarship experience started! This scholarship had a condition that I was aware of but I did not remember &amp;lsquo;my bad&amp;rsquo;, which was to have 2 years at least after graduation, they don&amp;rsquo;t count life time work experience&amp;hellip; which is very depressing!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t mind the terms and conditions but, I wonder what kind of term is this?? Why what different it is going to make having prior or post experience? I want to know if there is a reason behind this since most of the study abroad scholarship have it. I was deman ready and felt that this time I&amp;rsquo;d have it. Literally, everything was going smoothly and all documents were up and ready, guess it was not the right time for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclution&#34;&gt;Conclution
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just needed to share this here Hopefully someday I&amp;rsquo;ll have the answer! Maybe when the moment comes for me; this will be proof for me that everyone will get through. Also, I hope this helps somebody if face my situation. What makes me go through it.. is having a family, not any family a family that makes whatever in mind smaller and you can do it to a 3000 times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But as it is still new to overcoming this scholarship rejections I am taking it easy and I&amp;rsquo;ll take my time to apply for other scholarships. Since my goal is to complete my studies abroad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For next week&amp;rsquo;s blog.. I change the topic to a career perspective. Cause if I let this go on it will end it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;links&#34;&gt;Links
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📬 &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;mahaakab@gmail.com&#34; &gt; Email Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;☕ &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/c/MHCreator&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt; Coffee Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🌐 &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.fluentin3months.com/jlpt-n5-kanji/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;List for N5 Kanji&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;▶️ &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@Takashi_teaches_Japanese/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Mina no Nihon GO Book&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;▶️ &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@LearnJapaneseKanji/playlists&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Memorise Kanji&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🌐 &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://tadoku.org/japanese/en/free-books-en/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Japanese Short Stories Free&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How Anime Inspired My Passion for the Japanese Language | Part 2</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/my-fifth-post/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 18:42:53 +0500</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/my-fifth-post/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/0005.png" alt="Featured image of post How Anime Inspired My Passion for the Japanese Language | Part 2" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the background of How Anime Inspired My Passion for the Japanese Language. In this blog post, I&amp;rsquo;ll share the resources that helped me learn the Japanese language for the self-study method.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the end of this blog post, I&amp;rsquo;ll share my N5 test result&amp;hellip; I got the result today morning 31 Jan 2025. And why I am doing the JLPT exam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;resourses-to-help-study-japanese&#34;&gt;Resourses to help study Japanese:
&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actually, as I begin to check what are the best resources for self-study or is good to just find a course online or attend a language course at a campus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll start with the latter since the first takes a lot to explain:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For face-to-face campus:&lt;/strong&gt;
There is an amazing university called &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.numl.edu.pk/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;NUML University&lt;/a&gt;, this uni specializes in Languages there are almost all languages that a person interested in can learn, and they provide various levels starting with certificates to diplomas also, some have Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degrees and few have Master Degree. But first, check their website to know more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But when it came to me, their times were not suitable for me because I was working. So, I said let me try self-study.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Self Study:&lt;/strong&gt;
I did my first online course for &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://minato-jf.jp/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Japanese Language&lt;/a&gt; I did Marugoto for a while. Eventually, I decided last year in July that I would do the JLPT Exam, yet I was confused between N5 and N4 since N3 I felt there was a lot on me. In the end, my decision was N5.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, I have missed the date for July 2024. I had to wait and apply for the Des 2024 Test. This gives me like 6 months to really prepare for the first time. I planned to check some videos on Youtube by people who have taken the exam, to create my plan:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Find a Study Book, I have picked from the two famous books Ginki and &lt;strong&gt;Mina no Nihon Go&lt;/strong&gt; the latter. The Study book had everything but, I have put all the required Kanji for N5 in a section in my copy so I can memorize them in my free time, a section for every lesson grammar, and a section for vocabulary with answering book questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have chosen to study for 4 hours but to behonest life won&amp;rsquo;t relieve you for it grap so when I could not I had to make up time to waste hours. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t finish the whole book before the exam, I have just finished 5 first lessons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I did not focus on writing much and speaking since these skills are not tested in the exam, it&amp;rsquo;s a Muiltbull choice question, for Reading, Grammar, vocabulary, and lastly Listening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note&lt;/strong&gt; You can enhance your skills of speaking and writing if you wish when preparing for the exam but you need to put extra time and effort. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t because my life experience is different from you all, and I respect it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please find the Links to resources in the &lt;strong&gt;Links Section&lt;/strong&gt; I used to help me study the language on my own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, after I have given you some brief about my studying plan I still choose learning by myself for my N3 JLPT. My reason for studying Japanese it may sound silly but I want to watch anime without subtitles and as I am trying to find an opportunity to complete my higher studies in Japan, I want to be comfortable with the language.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My result of the 1st Des 2024 Exam as shown, it shows that I did not pass! But considering everything I have mentioned above, I see an achievement and I don&amp;rsquo;t want to bring the maximum score I want the passing which is 80. Yet, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t have them this time.
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/0005p.png&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;alt text&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, My plan now is to prepare for N3 as I have a whole year to prepare for the exam. And if I did not pass that one I&amp;rsquo;ll repeat it till I get the passing score.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just take it easy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;links&#34;&gt;Links
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📬 &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;mahaakab@gmail.com&#34; &gt; Email Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;☕ &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/c/MHCreator&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt; Coffee Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🌐 &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.fluentin3months.com/jlpt-n5-kanji/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;List for N5 Kanji&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;▶️ &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@Takashi_teaches_Japanese/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Mina no Nihon GO Book&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;▶️ &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/@LearnJapaneseKanji/playlists&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Memorise Kanji&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;🌐 &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://tadoku.org/japanese/en/free-books-en/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Japanese Short Stories Free&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>How Anime Inspired My Passion for the Japanese Language</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/my-forth-post/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 16:52:13 +0500</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/my-forth-post/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/0004.png" alt="Featured image of post How Anime Inspired My Passion for the Japanese Language" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From the topic, today&amp;rsquo;s blog is about Using entertainment for language skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I remember!😇 After high school I was easily taking my life, cause all I knew back then was that my life hit a dead wall for some reason I will keep off this time, to focus on today&amp;rsquo;s topic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was around 2011 and 2012 or maybe 2013, when I had one main idea in my mind which was how I can develop my language skills. My main focus was the English Language because my mother tongue wasn&amp;rsquo;t English.😏&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To find the resources to help myself find new vocals; there were English songs and TV series! But what was on TV I didn&amp;rsquo;t like it!🥸 Because the Internet had amazing options like a series called Supernatural, Sam was my favorite! I saw the first of two seasons on TV and when I checked the Internet they were during the 3rd or 4th season, I needed to catch on&amp;hellip;😎&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yet, back then I didn&amp;rsquo;t know anything about torrents!😁 The websites I had were paid to watch not free &amp;ldquo;I know nothing is supposed to be free for copywrites&amp;rdquo;. But It&amp;rsquo;s not me it was away at that time and it was normal at the time. Also, there were some illegal websites for a person like me who could not pay to watch for free&amp;hellip;.!😮‍💨&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The bummer was they did not have American series they had &lt;strong&gt;Korean drama, Japanese drama, and Anime!!!!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;here-is-how-everything-started&#34;&gt;Here Is How Everything Started!😳
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I began watching first with Korean Drama; Coffee Prince my all-time favorite. Then Boys Before Flowers&amp;hellip; and some that I don&amp;rsquo;t remember now. It helped me gain new words every day cause Korean I wasn&amp;rsquo;t understand so, I checked the subtitles to know what happening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This really helped me be good at Reading, Writing, Speaking, and Listening;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reading: I had to read the subtitles to understand what was happening. Any word I did not know I used to ask my cousin and the early Google translator which use to suck. I don&amp;rsquo;t remember using a dictionary&amp;hellip; hmmm I don&amp;rsquo;t remember.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Writing: taking up words and writing them on my notes was that was all. And I used to use them in writing on my FB Page, massaging my friends &amp;hellip; that was it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking: I begin using them with my own language! This helped me know how to pronounce it correctly. It got me some laughs on but no worries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Listening: this was tricky since by listening to Korean a lot I really became familiar with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Brilliant Idea Come-up&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Why don&amp;rsquo;t I start also learning Korean! I&amp;rsquo;ll hit two birds with one stone since learning languages has become my goal. And I did it and started learning the alphabet and watching. I kept doing this for a while.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then my friend N &amp;lsquo;&amp;lsquo;her name starts with N&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;, to avoid any confusion. She told me to watch an anime with her and I did not resist yet, I welcomed the idea. Gosick was the one I began with my friend watching the anime. After that, I am still watching anime. I started loving Japan, Japanese culture, and language.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-think-ending-this-blog-here-is-a-good-idea&#34;&gt;I Think Ending This Blog Here, Is A Good Idea!
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This fancy kind of story is here.🤭 I can proudly say that I have passed my IELTS exam with a very pleasant mark and I did my N5 first JLPT exam on Dec 2024; still waiting for the results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can have another special blog on My favorite anime, How I prepare for the N5 JLPT exam, and maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll share my IELTS success story! I may share my own tips for learning languages as self-study.And the best resources that I used from ppl I saw as experts in it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, till next Friday, take it easy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;links&#34;&gt;Links
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📬 &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;mahaakab@gmail.com&#34; &gt; Email Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;☕ &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/c/MHCreator&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt; Coffee Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
