<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>CreativeEntrepreneur on MH Creator</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/creativeentrepreneur/</link>
        <description>Recent content in CreativeEntrepreneur on MH Creator</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 17:50:59 +0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/creativeentrepreneur/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Who am I? Why! and What I want to Do</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/my-third-post/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 17:50:59 +0500</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/my-third-post/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/0003.png" alt="Featured image of post Who am I? Why! and What I want to Do" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;who&#34;&gt;Who!
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After 13 years of working a job, freelance, then changing locations another corporate job, getting fired for the first time, and a new job, another new job. And I quit. My mindset become clear to start building a personal brand for myself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Away for my personal growth journey, I am Maha, 32 years old. Living on earth in a country name Pakistan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;why&#34;&gt;Why!
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;As I mentioned above what I think good experience from my working life. I have decided to do what I used to do to grow other people&amp;rsquo;s brands, clients, and companies. I want to use my talents and skills for myself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First I want to create a showcase from myself to everyone else who is hesitating.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If it git to bad idea then, it’s proof to myself that I Fucked up.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It’s Now or Later Not now or never. But I decided for now to do IT.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-i-want-to-do&#34;&gt;What I want To do!
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I said it earlier in my first post, but here I want to specify it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My Plan:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Create a webpage with Hugo themes and Github. Checked it ^ this was like going through hell, gladly I did it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to start Digital drawing and manga creation. Post about my leveling up here too, or maybe open a Youtube channel!! I still don&amp;rsquo;t know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have two freelance brands one is in Photography and the other is making candles. In photography, I have a ground to stand on but candles going to be new. So I need to build it correctly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before the last, I like learning new cultures and languages so I am doing Japanese now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lastly, I don’t know what I’ll have as an interest in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know having multitasking with multiple interests is not a good idea! Yet, being inspiraed by Elon Musk, as he go&amp;rsquo;s through different companies in one day, motivated me. So, I’m not him I can not do all in one day, instead, I’ll do is to give all the needed time for one thing in time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My Priorities are, Learning Japanese for JLPT/N3 before upcoming July 2025 for like 1-2 hours a day. I can also have another thing like drawing since my first drawing table will arrive today Saturday 18, 2025, to give 2-3 hours is doable too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, I make sure to have a separate blog post for each thing I mentioned above, to give a background and share the present and future perspectives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;link&#34;&gt;Link
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;☕ &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/c/MHCreator&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt; Coffee Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
