<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>HealthyRelationships on MH Creator</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/healthyrelationships/</link>
        <description>Recent content in HealthyRelationships on MH Creator</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 15:17:19 +0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/healthyrelationships/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Why Women Shouldn’t Lower Their Standards in Relationships</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/Why-Women-Shouldn%E2%80%99t-Lower-Their-Standards-in-Relationships/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 15:17:19 +0500</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/Why-Women-Shouldn%E2%80%99t-Lower-Their-Standards-in-Relationships/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/0015.png" alt="Featured image of post Why Women Shouldn’t Lower Their Standards in Relationships" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this blog post, I want to argue a point of view that I have been hearing a lot for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Which is:&lt;/strong&gt; Women need to lower their standards, especially when it comes to relationships!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I want to suggest something to all the guys who say this and relationship coaches — especially: why don’t you say this instead? &amp;ldquo;Read Below.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;main-points&#34;&gt;Main Points
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why don&amp;rsquo;t you say to the guys who cannot find an understandable woman:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Be polite. No need for money or status — representing yourself with politeness is one way to get through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Humor is an amazing personality trait to have! But know how to use it properly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Education degree is good, but if you have good understanding of your surroundings and how to utilize problem solving with critical thinking in a calm way, then I am sorry not sorry — put your degree in a cup of water and drink it. Maybe it will be useful. Hypothetically, a way to at least drink the knowledge since your brilliant mind could not have the benefits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do work on upgrading your knowledge, and these days you have plenty of ways to do it. Read a book, watch documentaries, involve yourself in workshops, or learn a craft. Make yourself useful to her. I know people who have nothing to brag about except their good behavior and usefulness, and women agree on what they have. And I can see that she is way smarter than him, and I believe he knows it — yet he is not downsizing her. Instead, he is also using her knowledge for his life tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lastly, guys, as you are asking for things, make sure you meet what she asks for! Because this is what made the standard higher.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Girls, have your standard met. If he agrees and asks for time to meet your standard, understand him — give him time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What I mean here by standards is not money, status, or fame. No, I mean behavior-wise, maturity, emotional intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;1- Tip: Ask her, who is your favorite actor? If she says anything about the character he played, listen to her — she is telling you about the way of treating her, okay!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If she said otherwise, then it is up to you if you want to stay or leave. She is materialistic if you are thinking to have an understanding one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2- Tip: Watch this &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0406046/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;movie&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt13911628/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;series&lt;/a&gt;. Look please at what the male character did to show his usefulness and understanding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;-mh&#34;&gt;– MH
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;links&#34;&gt;Links
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📬 &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;mahaakab@gmail.com&#34; &gt; Email Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;☕ &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/c/MHCreator&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt; Coffee Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
