<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Boundaries on MH Creator</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/boundaries/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Boundaries on MH Creator</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 03:00:51 +0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/boundaries/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Caught in the Middle: Why I Don’t Interfere in Loved Ones&#39; Disagreements Anymore</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/my-seventeen-post/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 03:00:51 +0500</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/my-seventeen-post/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/0017.png" alt="Featured image of post Caught in the Middle: Why I Don’t Interfere in Loved Ones&#39; Disagreements Anymore" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Okay&amp;hellip; I think when I started blogging, I’ve started noticing the things I go through each week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because before blogging, no matter what I had gone through — I really could not recall it. 0_0 hehehe&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, it is one of the advantages of blogging, I guess.
(Cause no matter whoever said it — I wouldn’t believe it. But when doing it — it makes sense).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let me dive in — into this blog post’s topic!
Which is something that happened in my life in the last two weeks.
That’s why I mentioned blogging helps me remember when things happen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thus, the topic is:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do not interfere or take sides when two individuals you love have a fight or misunderstanding.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;main-points&#34;&gt;Main Points
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I won’t spill all the details, since it’s not my matter — and I didn’t ask their permission to talk about it.
But it was something between a loving father and a loving daughter. Both of them are amazing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But one of them wanted a certain life decision, and the other couldn’t bear it —
since it wasn’t something they were satisfied with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And I took the side of one of them — maybe because I wanted to fix something that happened in the past. Yet… it was the present moment!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, I took the side immediately, without really listening to the other side.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plus — things really escalated, my fears and anger got me blind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I stopped sleeping, eating well, and thinking while sleeping! I say this because I remember sleeping on the same thought and waking up on it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Even worse — I couldn’t do my daily tasks or at least live the way I want to.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve learned a lot from this life lesson. Not because I was a brilliant, wise thinker. No!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yeah, I felt that something wasn’t working — and I had a person who really was there and gave me the real talk that even shut me up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, having a person in your life — family member or friend — who can bring you back to your senses and logical mind? It’s a blessing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To end this blog here, I’ll just say:
I’ve learned the lesson and dis-attached myself from other people’s life experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just take it easy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;-mh&#34;&gt;– MH
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;links&#34;&gt;Links
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📬 &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;mahaakab@gmail.com&#34; &gt; Email Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;☕ &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/c/MHCreator&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt; Coffee Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
