<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Time Management Boundaries on MH Creator</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/time-management-boundaries/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Time Management Boundaries on MH Creator</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 21:16:24 +0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/time-management-boundaries/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Appreciation Begins Within: A Self-Reflection</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/Appreciation-Begins-Within:-A-Self-Reflection/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 21:16:24 +0500</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/Appreciation-Begins-Within:-A-Self-Reflection/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/0018.png" alt="Featured image of post Appreciation Begins Within: A Self-Reflection" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When was the last time you have appreciated yourself!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This has been the idea I’ve been thinking about since I woke up today. Before writing the blog post, I had to read these &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://thomsinger.medium.com/how-to-appreciate-yourself-88947f58ec3b&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;heart soothing words&lt;/a&gt; by
Thom Singer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because the moment you feel unappreciated — especially the need from the exterior world — it’s a sign that you are not doing it for yourself enough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;main-points&#34;&gt;Main Points
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;What I have been thinking today is that there are a few things — when I do them — I know and feel that I am not appreciating myself by doing them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When a close person sees that my time is okay to be wasted. Yet it’s not&amp;hellip; And they know my reaction is always yes. I love helping people, and I can do more even when I am busy or overwhelmed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But this has got to stop!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many things in my life are on hold! Because I have no time management when it comes to loved ones. I am fully dividing my time for others and taking only a small portion of it for my own tasks — and at the end, lots of unfinished tasks build up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have also seen that when it&amp;rsquo;s my time to ask something from them, they put me on hold or tell me they’re not free or will schedule it for another time — no matter how small the task is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know that I have been in a discovery mode since this year began! I am rethinking many aspects and ideas that I thought were my life rules and principles. But as human nature shows, change is the only factor we rely on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, as I’ve started to love myself — the physical body — I need to change my mental behavior toward myself. By really focusing on my needs to learn, and putting time into doing the things I want to do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to act with love toward myself. So, I’ll just be taking it easy this time.
Thanks for reading.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;mh-creator&#34;&gt;MH Creator
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;links&#34;&gt;Links
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📬 &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;mahaakab@gmail.com&#34; &gt; Email Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;☕ &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/c/MHCreator&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt; Coffee Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
