<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Cycle-Breaking Motherhood on MH Creator</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/cycle-breaking-motherhood/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Cycle-Breaking Motherhood on MH Creator</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 19:36:23 +0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/cycle-breaking-motherhood/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Why Some People Shouldn’t Have Kids!</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/Why-Some-People-Shouldn%E2%80%99t-Have-Kids/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 19:36:23 +0500</pubDate>
        
        <guid>http://localhost:1313/Why-Some-People-Shouldn%E2%80%99t-Have-Kids/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="http://localhost:1313/0014.png" alt="Featured image of post Why Some People Shouldn’t Have Kids!" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;intro&#34;&gt;Intro
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don’t know much about motherhood — but I do know it’s very hard.
In this blog post, I’ll try to explain where I stand on the matter, because for a long time, it has been one of my biggest fears.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;main-points&#34;&gt;Main Points
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Growing up, I saw the difference between being just a parent-mother and being a real mother. A parent-mother only cares about bringing kids into the world. A mother, on the other hand, takes care of everything — from a child’s appearance to their inner emotional and mental well-being.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After witnessing this contrast, I promised myself that I wouldn’t bring anyone into this world through me. Life continued to show me that parenting is not a game. And I believe these parent-mothers, who only focus on birthing children, often cause long-term harm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because when their kids grow up and start to wake up to reality, they go through grief — some break down, others spend years just trying to figure themselves out, usually without any healthy emotional tools.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are a few real-life examples:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How to be okay with yourself: If your subconscious is wired to believe that you are the problem, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to feel peace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How to understand and deal with fear: When your body and mind are used to living in constant fear, even peaceful moments feel like a trap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How to trust yourself: This one is the hardest. You think you’ve faced the issue and solved it — but then something takes you back to square one, deeper into the original wound.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finding a life partner: You may meet the right person — but instead of building a calm future together, your unresolved wounds make the relationship full of unnecessary obstacles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let me define a few terms, from my point of view:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parent-Mother: Someone only concerned with reproduction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mother: Someone who knows she can&amp;rsquo;t be everything, but chooses to seek help — from the father, grandmothers, grandfathers, aunts, and uncles — to raise her child in a healthy way. By telling them her way some they can conturbite right. She focuses on understanding rather than always being right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s all for today. Just take it easy. 🌱&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;-mh&#34;&gt;– MH
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;links&#34;&gt;Links
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;📬 &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;mahaakab@gmail.com&#34; &gt; Email Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;☕ &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.patreon.com/c/MHCreator&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt; Coffee Me &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
